<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Honesty on Superbad Software</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/honesty/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Honesty on Superbad Software</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 18:50:14 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/honesty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lying Expectations</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/lying-expectations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 18:50:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/lying-expectations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;lying-for-good&#34;&gt;Lying for good&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been mulling ideas about lying over for a couple days. Telling the truth is the easiest way forward, generally, but&#xA;there are edge cases. Like the Japanese grandmother where her family knew she had fatal cancer and lied to her. They let&#xA;her think she was healthy, so she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get sad and depressed and could live out her days without worrying about&#xA;the things that come with a stage 4 diagnosis. I think she ended up living a couple years longer than was expected. Is&#xA;this a good lie? For her, maybe. If I was her family, I would have felt conflicted. I&amp;rsquo;ve been lied and been lied to&#xA;plenty of times through omission and being on either side doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel good. The spirit of the grandmother lie is good&#xA;but the follow through still results in bad feelings for family like me. That&amp;rsquo;s expected, death is rough in any situation&#xA;but I&amp;rsquo;m not really convinced its good. There&amp;rsquo;s a certain type of person and situation where it is the best, most moral&#xA;action but that situation probably wouldn&amp;rsquo;t involve me. Lying for a good reason, and getting a good result - thats good.&#xA;Lying for a bad reason and getting a bad result - I suppose thats good in terms of expectations but the morality isn&amp;rsquo;t.&#xA;The other variations good reason bad result/bad reason good result, are big problems. This isnt really going anywhere.&#xA;Life has gotten a lot simpler. A whole category of problems has been removed after choosing to be honest at all times,&#xA;even if you might hurt someone&amp;rsquo;s feelings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
