<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>You don&#39;t start out writing good stuff on Superbad Software</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in You don&#39;t start out writing good stuff on Superbad Software</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 12:37:05 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Extra Stuff</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/extra-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 12:37:05 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/extra-stuff/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-back-of-house-is-crazy-but-simple-to-be-focused&#34;&gt;The back of house is crazy but simple to be focused&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The past few weeks I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing the truck, learning porter, grill, sandwiches and office work. Also taking temps and&#xA;doing other assorted paperwork needed to run the restaurant daily, and freezer pulls. Doing truck is hard some days&#xA;because youre in a -10deg freezer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;things-to-do&#34;&gt;things to do&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;131 principle. one problem, three solutions, one recommendation. 80/20 rule for standup, staff talk for 80 of the time&#xA;management speaks 20. curiosity, systems and goals, measurement. So I think I&amp;rsquo;m going to implement standups, 4 mins.&#xA;Ask about the previous service, ask about today and problems and solutions and focus. Ask about things they did wrong&#xA;and what they should do to avoid that, talk about accountability. See if this has an impact over the next week and if it&#xA;does then bring it up for everyone(managers) to implement. Invite them in for it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staying late</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/stayinglate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 20:42:13 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/stayinglate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;people-come-and-people-go&#34;&gt;People come and people go&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I feel like theres been a few people that have been let go and a few that have quit. I think one person walked out this&#xA;evening. Its not a bad job, its really fun. I think the manager staff is a little new at the game though. Its their first&#xA;time being in charge and they have an idea of how they want to manage but dont know how to do it. Most likely, none of&#xA;them have ever had a good boss before, so they dont know what that feels like and dont have an idea of how to get there.&#xA;Sometimes I give little pep talks to them, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if that helps. I&amp;rsquo;m in an odd position, im just a worker,&#xA;nobody bothers me, nothing bothers me, I do whats expected and fill my time with useful tasks, seek out new tasks and&#xA;information and ways to help, and do that. I know I&amp;rsquo;m probably older than all the managers and I suppose that gets me&#xA;some respect? I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how I fit into the picture, I train people on stations, I try to be a good role model. This&#xA;isn&amp;rsquo;t hard, especially since I&amp;rsquo;ve used the past year to straighten a lot of my life out by going to meetings and working&#xA;on myself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight Hours</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/eighthours/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 20:58:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/eighthours/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;its-a-lot-of-work&#34;&gt;Its a lot of work&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But I feel so satisfied. Working my body like this is really a cure all for me. For the past week and some change my&#xA;hours have been around 6-7 a day and today I think was the first time I did more than 8. 10 total. I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching&#xA;the national team and managers do 12 hour days for the past couple weeks and see how its taken a toll on them. I think&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m capable of doing those hard weeks, back to back, trying to get everyone up to speed. It sounds like fun to me. Right&#xA;now I&amp;rsquo;m learning a position called Set, Its like the expo for the front of the house and its a lot of work. A lot more&#xA;compared to the drive thru or register. Drive thru is like a little separate heaven where the madness doesn&amp;rsquo;t touch.&#xA;Sometimes you&amp;rsquo;ll get weirdos at the window but thats not that bad. The management staff is a bit wild. Theres some good&#xA;bosses and some anxious ones and some that are probably just plain bad. I wonder what Andrew thinks about how things are&#xA;going so far. I wish there was time to sit and talk with him but I dont think there is. Culver&amp;rsquo;s life is busy. Maybe one&#xA;day he&amp;rsquo;ll get someone to GM the place for him and then he&amp;rsquo;ll have time for other things, but from what I&amp;rsquo;ve seen of him&#xA;so far I think he&amp;rsquo;s a good boss.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 19:28:36 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/training/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-feel-good&#34;&gt;I feel good&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m surprised that things feel good. Work has been very good, lots of physical work but satisfying. Its so chaotic in the&#xA;restaurant, everyone is learning and trying to figure out the proper processes for everything. Its a mad house and I love&#xA;it. I &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; need to find a programming job though. I&amp;rsquo;ll want to keep doing this for the awesome food and custard and&#xA;everything fulfilling this job gives me, but I think realistically, I need that programmer money first. Maybe down the&#xA;line I can give owning a Culver&amp;rsquo;s a go, the pay for that is pretty good (300K-400K/yr) and its really a great company.&#xA;People I&amp;rsquo;ve met from the support or national team were excellent people, and one girl Hailey was outstanding. Patient&#xA;teacher, had all the good manager qualities, and also very attractive. She&amp;rsquo;s just become an owner at a store in Iowa&#xA;someplace.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Terilli</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/johnnyterilli/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 14:22:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/johnnyterilli/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;johnny-terilli-is-sad&#34;&gt;Johnny Terilli is sad&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some people can&amp;rsquo;t accept things as they are. They need a reason. Their inability to go through life without being able&#xA;to tell themselves &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m the best&amp;rdquo; is one of the glamorous causes of their problems. Lying to yourself, is an easy sport.&#xA;And its simple to win and convince yourself that your problems are so much worse than anyone else&amp;rsquo;s. You are a great hero,&#xA;a paragon, a martyr. Any input that says otherwise is due to a problem that someone else is going through. Its not honest,&#xA;its them working through their problems. The levels of manipulation and trickery these people will employ on others and&#xA;themselves to protect their precious story is one of the more depressive patterns in the world. If only you would dogfood&#xA;the things you were trying to say. You&amp;rsquo;d probably be better. But you don&amp;rsquo;t and you&amp;rsquo;re too old to change.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workweek</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/workweek/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 20:49:24 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/workweek/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-was-the-problem&#34;&gt;What was the problem?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Where was my drive to do anything? It was gone for about a year and now in a week its fallen into an appropriate position.&#xA;The only change was picking up a fast food job, which at first felt like a failure. But now it feels great, amazing&#xA;even. I can&amp;rsquo;t remember a time when I didn&amp;rsquo;t care about my job at all in this way. Not the way of &amp;ldquo;I dont care about it&#xA;so I won&amp;rsquo;t try to achieve&amp;rdquo;, but I don&amp;rsquo;t have any fear about the work, the people, any interaction. Any anxieties have&#xA;been replaced with a soaring confidence. The work is not difficult. I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to find a way to have fun in the&#xA;monotony and improve on parts of myself that I&amp;rsquo;d been neglecting. The job feels like a project. A side quest. Something&#xA;for the thrill of the experience. Which is a pretty good way to frame it. It would be so easy to judge myself as a failure&#xA;and the fast food job as proof. But I&amp;rsquo;ve done that a thousand times already. The past year of living in the void was&#xA;enough time to beat myself to death and then try not to. I&amp;rsquo;ll start with a slackbot to help people reschedule shifts.&#xA;And then if they like that, maybe theres other little things I can do to make the place better. Its so weird. I used&#xA;to have a bit of pride that I didn&amp;rsquo;t work a fast food job. That didn&amp;rsquo;t help much of anything though.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Feelings</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/employment-feelings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 18:00:09 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/employment-feelings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;not-having-a-job&#34;&gt;Not having a job&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My cat is big. Not really fat, just big. Big boned I suppose and about twenty pounds. A buff, which is another term for&#xA;light orange, American short-hair. The other week I spent a couple of days cat sitting for my friend and I got to spend&#xA;a lot of quality time with their cat. Her name was Surreal. She was a sweet, cuddly indoor/outdoor cat who knew that I&#xA;was her friend and a welcome source of petting, playing, love and affection. It was great. As far as cat software goes&#xA;she had some A+ cat code installed. Its always funny when I spend time around other cats, then come home to my cat and&#xA;remember how much of a monster she is compared to regular cats. Not quite Maine Coon, but still, quite enough. Nala, my&#xA;cat, is skittish, a big scaredy. She doesn&amp;rsquo;t trust anyone except me, which makes me feel special and its sort of&#xA;endearing, but I wish she would be more confident. This is a criticism I&amp;rsquo;ve heard made about me in recent years and,&#xA;yeah, I wish so too. I can remember the overflowing confidence of my 20s and I just don&amp;rsquo;t feel that way anymore. Sure&#xA;I can fake it, but being honest is so much easier. I dont want to trick people into liking a &amp;lsquo;for show&amp;rsquo; version of&#xA;myself. Did I teach my cat my un-confidence? That cant be possible, could it? I don&amp;rsquo;t think so. I remember taking her to&#xA;the vet during covid and one trip changed her attitude forever. She &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;WAS&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; a confident and fearless kitten. Curious&#xA;and wild, but after the one trip to the vet she was so afraid. I used to be able to touch her hands and cut her nails and&#xA;now cutting her nails is impossible. During covid you had to drop your animal outisde the door of the vet and then come&#xA;back an hourish later to pick them up. I feel like if I was able to go inside and be with her in the vet this wouldnt have&#xA;happened. As a scared cat I still love her, but I wish she would demand pets, I wish I could carry her and that awkward&#xA;sounds wouldnt set her off. I&amp;rsquo;ve done a lot to try to un-shy her. Maybe she needs a little friend, a brother or a sister&#xA;to show her the ways of wild cat youth. To inspire her to relax and open up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lying Expectations</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/lying-expectations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 18:50:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/lying-expectations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;lying-for-good&#34;&gt;Lying for good&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been mulling ideas about lying over for a couple days. Telling the truth is the easiest way forward, generally, but&#xA;there are edge cases. Like the Japanese grandmother where her family knew she had fatal cancer and lied to her. They let&#xA;her think she was healthy, so she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get sad and depressed and could live out her days without worrying about&#xA;the things that come with a stage 4 diagnosis. I think she ended up living a couple years longer than was expected. Is&#xA;this a good lie? For her, maybe. If I was her family, I would have felt conflicted. I&amp;rsquo;ve been lied and been lied to&#xA;plenty of times through omission and being on either side doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel good. The spirit of the grandmother lie is good&#xA;but the follow through still results in bad feelings for family like me. That&amp;rsquo;s expected, death is rough in any situation&#xA;but I&amp;rsquo;m not really convinced its good. There&amp;rsquo;s a certain type of person and situation where it is the best, most moral&#xA;action but that situation probably wouldn&amp;rsquo;t involve me. Lying for a good reason, and getting a good result - thats good.&#xA;Lying for a bad reason and getting a bad result - I suppose thats good in terms of expectations but the morality isn&amp;rsquo;t.&#xA;The other variations good reason bad result/bad reason good result, are big problems. This isnt really going anywhere.&#xA;Life has gotten a lot simpler. A whole category of problems has been removed after choosing to be honest at all times,&#xA;even if you might hurt someone&amp;rsquo;s feelings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working Plan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/working-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 19:36:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/working-plan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-think-this-is-the-thing-to-do&#34;&gt;I think this is the thing to do&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;rsquo;t had a job for over a year and I think Culver&amp;rsquo;s just hired me. This is going to be an interesting ride. I&#xA;remember feeling a kind of pride for not having worked a fast food job in the past. Is this a success? It doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel&#xA;like it. This is going to be a wide cast of characters, kids in high school, 60 year olds, lots of attitudes and hungry&#xA;grumps. Good thing I have access to emotions like anger and frustration again. Typically, I&amp;rsquo;m a very patient person and&#xA;this doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel like it will be a problem, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know everything, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been wrong before. Having something&#xA;to do while getting my programming chops back is a benefit and I suppose that is a victory. The past year has been a&#xA;lot of emotions and stagnation. An inability to move anything. This is movement. That&amp;rsquo;s good. It&amp;rsquo;s something.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanity is not statistical</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/sanity-not-statistical/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/sanity-not-statistical/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;there-is-a-lot-of-feelings&#34;&gt;There is a lot of feelings&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After a huge failure last year of breaking down, going to rehab, quitting a great job, navigating an impossible family&#xA;relationship, where do I find the motivation to do anything? Laying down and giving up is such an inviting idea. I&amp;rsquo;ve&#xA;been trying to avoid using anger and frustration as a motivator. Could I move through the world on positive emotions?&#xA;I can&amp;rsquo;t, at least not right now. Most of my will is dedicated to trying not to go down negative mental rabbit holes that&#xA;lead to me doing nothing. If I can fight off the bad feelings then I can move - this way doesnt really work. When&#xA;everything feels so negative its impossible to think myself out of it. One thing Ive learned is that the opposite is&#xA;true. A simple &amp;ldquo;fake it till you make it&amp;rdquo; attitude. Just act like you&amp;rsquo;re happy, do the things a happy person would do&#xA;and then your thinking will follow you there over time. This is a weird point in time right now. I&amp;rsquo;ve just gotten off&#xA;anti-depressants and the access to more emotions has come back. Feelings like anger and frustration have replaced a&#xA;detatched, zombie-like ambivalence. As my brain levels back out, the emotions yo-yo just like when I first got on them.&#xA;Using negative feelings as motivation felt like a failure a couple weeks ago, but now what else am I supposed to do with&#xA;it?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I can&#39;t think myself into good acting but I can act myself into good thinking.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/language-perfect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/language-perfect/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;betrayal-and-character-assassination&#34;&gt;Betrayal and character assassination&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why do people punish themselves? Pride. Sometimes in weird places, sometimes in obvious ones. Write from the scar, not&#xA;from the wound. Itll be too emotional if its from an open wound. Thats pretty good advice. Getting away for a few days&#xA;is great to reflect and figure out what I&amp;rsquo;m doing with myself. Its been a lot of nothing, starving, depression. Not good.&#xA;Having someone to yell at you and rile you up is a strange bonus. I can use any negative feelings as fuel to get things&#xA;done, but I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to avoid that for a while. Can&amp;rsquo;t I find enough positive emotions to use as a motivation&#xA;source? It doesnt look like it, at least not right now. It was a decent experiment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s a beautiful thing, the destruction of words</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/destruction-of-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/destruction-of-words/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;not-convincing-enough&#34;&gt;Not convincing enough&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Trying to convince someone not to lie is a rough game. Especially if the lies are to themselves. The amount of depression&#xA;and gaslighting that&amp;rsquo;s come out of me trying to get my mother to be honest has been a challenge. It can&amp;rsquo;t be done.&#xA;Changing other people, if they don&amp;rsquo;t want to, is impossible, and if its not then its probably through some illegal means.&#xA;I suppose I need to be more selfish. Not think about this. Just be a good person and not try to control anyone else, even&#xA;if I&amp;rsquo;m right, or trying to help or whatever reason I can come up with. Patience, honesty, serenity feel like easy goals&#xA;until something pops up. There&amp;rsquo;s always some event or topic or trigger where that goes out the window. If I ate better&#xA;I would be better, stress will take my appetite away and the lack of food will fuel my anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who controls the past.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/controls-the-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/controls-the-past/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-have-too-many-expectations-of-my-mom&#34;&gt;I have too many expectations of my mom&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shes getting old and her judgement is beginning to go. The other month she was sure she&amp;rsquo;d been texting Elon Musk and he&#xA;was waiting on her gift cards so he could finish delivering a Tesla and 100K to her. Part of me is fighting with her,&#xA;trying to reason things out with her to show her how to watch out for traps like this. Another part is fighting reality,&#xA;I don&amp;rsquo;t want to admit that her thinking is so compromised. That its just going to get harder for her to understand me.&#xA;She&amp;rsquo;s doing it too, she&amp;rsquo;s fighting the fact she&amp;rsquo;s going to die, that her thinking has gotten worse, constantly telling&#xA;herself she&amp;rsquo;s not as bad as someone else in the Assisted Living Facility. It must be terrible to be in your 70s and be&#xA;afraid of death and aging. Knowing that your father and sister suffered from dementia and that you are next in line. If&#xA;I don&amp;rsquo;t think about it then its not happening. I wish that were the case. I wish I could do something to remove her&#xA;insecurities, find her some friends, stop her from judging herself and others. She&amp;rsquo;s been alone too long and her pride&#xA;is being used to keep her ego afloat. I can just try to show her I love her, even though she won&amp;rsquo;t understand it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;contra-vagos&#34;&gt;Contra vagos&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lorem &lt;em&gt;markdownum notam si&lt;/em&gt; lintea meque certa &lt;a href=&#34;#cohibentem-iuvenaliter&#34;&gt;en meumque&#xA;illis&lt;/a&gt;, diu fatigant, nec praedae concustodita arcet.&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;#nemorisque-urimur-violentus&#34;&gt;Paviunt castris&lt;/a&gt; cur errat ventis causa! Silvas&#xA;sine satis vocat praedam moverat, precor, non sola bovis neque mihi. Primum&#xA;utilis nympham, et certus amplexas Deiphobum palmis credas ambo, nec.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Excidit gente, si orat suo quaeque dura Calydon nata? Pars auro post stetit&#xA;adfusique imis amplexus. Agmina per fabricator&#xA;mittere Erymanthon habetque tot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cineres Nile ipsa&lt;/strong&gt; origine discurrunt adest Unde, et quem clausus, imo,&#xA;virens quoque tales, potuit. Ingentes insilit corpore nutricis praebebat roganti&#xA;licuit. Denique a vestros adulantum in bella lina parte et arte generi di igitur&#xA;quis, digitis pedes. Cum resonant tamen, namque in anxia. Non nostri trahens&#xA;ancora.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
