<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Depression on Superbad Software</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/depression/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Depression on Superbad Software</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/depression/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sanity is not statistical</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/sanity-not-statistical/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/sanity-not-statistical/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;there-is-a-lot-of-feelings&#34;&gt;There is a lot of feelings&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After a huge failure last year of breaking down, going to rehab, quitting a great job, navigating an impossible family&#xA;relationship, where do I find the motivation to do anything? Laying down and giving up is such an inviting idea. I&amp;rsquo;ve&#xA;been trying to avoid using anger and frustration as a motivator. Could I move through the world on positive emotions?&#xA;I can&amp;rsquo;t, at least not right now. Most of my will is dedicated to trying not to go down negative mental rabbit holes that&#xA;lead to me doing nothing. If I can fight off the bad feelings then I can move - this way doesnt really work. When&#xA;everything feels so negative its impossible to think myself out of it. One thing Ive learned is that the opposite is&#xA;true. A simple &amp;ldquo;fake it till you make it&amp;rdquo; attitude. Just act like you&amp;rsquo;re happy, do the things a happy person would do&#xA;and then your thinking will follow you there over time. This is a weird point in time right now. I&amp;rsquo;ve just gotten off&#xA;anti-depressants and the access to more emotions has come back. Feelings like anger and frustration have replaced a&#xA;detatched, zombie-like ambivalence. As my brain levels back out, the emotions yo-yo just like when I first got on them.&#xA;Using negative feelings as motivation felt like a failure a couple weeks ago, but now what else am I supposed to do with&#xA;it?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
