<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Family on Superbad Software</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/family/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Family on Superbad Software</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s a beautiful thing, the destruction of words</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/destruction-of-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/destruction-of-words/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;not-convincing-enough&#34;&gt;Not convincing enough&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Trying to convince someone not to lie is a rough game. Especially if the lies are to themselves. The amount of depression&#xA;and gaslighting that&amp;rsquo;s come out of me trying to get my mother to be honest has been a challenge. It can&amp;rsquo;t be done.&#xA;Changing other people, if they don&amp;rsquo;t want to, is impossible, and if its not then its probably through some illegal means.&#xA;I suppose I need to be more selfish. Not think about this. Just be a good person and not try to control anyone else, even&#xA;if I&amp;rsquo;m right, or trying to help or whatever reason I can come up with. Patience, honesty, serenity feel like easy goals&#xA;until something pops up. There&amp;rsquo;s always some event or topic or trigger where that goes out the window. If I ate better&#xA;I would be better, stress will take my appetite away and the lack of food will fuel my anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who controls the past.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/controls-the-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/controls-the-past/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-have-too-many-expectations-of-my-mom&#34;&gt;I have too many expectations of my mom&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shes getting old and her judgement is beginning to go. The other month she was sure she&amp;rsquo;d been texting Elon Musk and he&#xA;was waiting on her gift cards so he could finish delivering a Tesla and 100K to her. Part of me is fighting with her,&#xA;trying to reason things out with her to show her how to watch out for traps like this. Another part is fighting reality,&#xA;I don&amp;rsquo;t want to admit that her thinking is so compromised. That its just going to get harder for her to understand me.&#xA;She&amp;rsquo;s doing it too, she&amp;rsquo;s fighting the fact she&amp;rsquo;s going to die, that her thinking has gotten worse, constantly telling&#xA;herself she&amp;rsquo;s not as bad as someone else in the Assisted Living Facility. It must be terrible to be in your 70s and be&#xA;afraid of death and aging. Knowing that your father and sister suffered from dementia and that you are next in line. If&#xA;I don&amp;rsquo;t think about it then its not happening. I wish that were the case. I wish I could do something to remove her&#xA;insecurities, find her some friends, stop her from judging herself and others. She&amp;rsquo;s been alone too long and her pride&#xA;is being used to keep her ego afloat. I can just try to show her I love her, even though she won&amp;rsquo;t understand it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
